[
    {
        "question": "List all files in directory ",
        "answer": "ls -la"
    },
    {
        "question": "Follow last part of file",
        "answer": "tail -f"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quiet program output",
        "answer": ">> /dev/null"
    },
    {
        "question": "Delete directory",
        "answer": "rm -r"
    },
    {
        "question": "Previous command as superuser",
        "answer": "sudo!!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Delete directory",
        "answer": "rm -r"
    },
    {
        "question": "Add program output to file",
        "answer": ">>"
    },
    {
        "question": "Create file",
        "answer": "touch"
    },
    {
        "question": "Make file executable",
        "answer": "chmod +x"
    },
    {
        "question": "Move 3 directories up",
        "answer": "cd ../../.."
    }
]
